slingcommunity.com 2013-05-27

# Slingbox Support - Privacy Policy

Get information about Sling Media’s privacy policy. 

**Introduction:  
**

Sling Media, Inc. (“Sling”) respects your privacy. This Privacy Statement applies to all of our web sites and our other products and services (collectively, “Sling Products”). This Privacy Statement explains what information we collect through the Sling Products, how we use that information, and what choices you have.

The Sling Products may contain links to other web sites. This Privacy Statement does not apply to the practices of any company or individual that Sling does not control, or any web sites or services that you link to from the Sling Products. You should use caution and review the privacy policies of any web sites or services that you visit from ours to learn more about their information practices.

Please take a few moments to read this Privacy Statement. By accessing the Sling Products, you agree to accept the terms and conditions of this Privacy Statement and are aware that our policies may evolve in the future as indicated below. In the event of a conflict between this Privacy Statement and our Terms of Use, our Terms of Use will control.

**What information we collect:  
**

In various places in connection with Sling Products, we collect “Personally Identifiable Information,” such as your name, postal address, telephone number, email address, or other information that can be used to identify you or contact you. For example, we collect this information when you sign up for our email newsletter, purchase or register a Slingbox product, register for a “Sling Account”, enter a sweepstakes or participate in promotions and give-aways. From time to time in the future we may offer additional features, services and promotional opportunities that would require you to submit Personally Identifiable Information to participate.

We also collect “Anonymous Information” such as your IP address, your ZIP code, your Media Access Control (MAC) address, your SlingFinder ID, the name you assigned to your Slingbox, the hardware and firmware version of your Slingbox, the type of browser you use, the pages on our websites that you visit, the identity of your broadcast television provider, the search terms that you enter, the advertisements that you click and the number and frequency of users of Sling Products. Anonymous Information will not be associated with Personally Identifiable Information.

Like many Internet sites, we also use “cookies” to collect information when you visit our website. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer and is stored on your hard drive. When you visit our websites the cookie identifies your computer to us so that you do not have to re-register each time you visit. We also use cookies to measure the traffic to our site and its different services and features, and other miscellaneous uses.

We do not intend that children will use the Sling Products. We do not solicit or knowingly collect information from children under 13 years old, nor will we knowingly accept registration from them.

**How we use the information we collect:  
**

We use Personally Identifiable Information that you provide us for such purposes as responding to your requests for information, products or services, customizing the advertising and content you see, and communicating with you about our offerings. For example, if you sign up for our email newsletter, we will send the newsletter to the email address you provided. If you so choose, we will also use Personally Identifiable Information to send you information about products and services that may be of interest to you. Later on in this Privacy Statement, we provide you with more information on what choices you have.

We use Anonymous Information to determine how people use the Sling Products. For example this data tells us information including how often users click on our advertisements, which files are downloaded most frequently, and which components or areas of Sling Products are the most popular. Analyzing this data allows us to improve the offerings on and performance of Sling Products.

**How we share information:  
**

We sometimes use third parties to help with some aspects of the Sling Products, such as delivering content, processing payments and providing marketing assistance. When we supply Personally Identifiable Information to these third parties, we require them to use it only for the function they are helping us with.

We aggregate the Anonymous Information that we collect and exchange it with advertisers and other partners who are interested in the use and performance of the Sling Products.  We share this type of data so that our partners also may provide you with an optimal user experience and better understand how users access the Sling Products.

We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information as required by law, or if in our judgment it is necessary to protect Sling or our employees or users from harm, loss or liability. If we merge with or are acquired by another company or we sell substantially all of our assets, the acquiror or resulting company will receive and may continue to use the information you have provided as described in this policy. In the unlikely event we cease operation or enter bankruptcy, your information may be transferred to and used by another company that acquires our assets or offers similar or related products or services.  You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any such acquiror or successor may continue to use your information as set forth in this policy.

Personally Identifiable Information you can access:   

We allow you to access the following information about you for the purpose of viewing, and in certain situations, updating that information. This list will change as Sling Products change. You may currently access the following information:   

  * user profile, and
  * user preferences.  

**What choices you have:  
**

When you register for the Sling Products, you have the option of checking a box to tell us that you do not want us to send you any information about our products and services, or that you do not want to receive information from our partners and others about products and services that might interest you. We will keep track of your decision in our database. Even if you choose not to receive information from us, we reserve the right to communicate with you on matters we consider especially important.  Further, please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Statement, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Sling Products, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes.

You are able to add or update certain information on pages, such as those listed in the “Personally Identifiable Information you can access” section above. When you update information, however, we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. 

You delete your account by calling Sling’s customer support line at (877) 467.5464.  Please note that some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account.

**Postings:  
**

If you use our bulletin boards, post user comments regarding content available through the Sling Products, or engage in similar activity, please remember that anything you post is publicly available. Portions of your user profile will also be available to other users of our websites.

**Security:  
**

During sessions in which you give us information such as credit card numbers, we encrypt your transmissions using SSL (“Secure Sockets Layer”), and other security technology. This guards against interception of the information while it is on the Internet. We keep the Personally Identifiable Information you provide on servers that are protected by firewalls and other technological means against intrusion or unauthorized access. They are located in a physically secure facility, however, there is no such thing as “perfect security” on the Internet. We rely on you to select passwords that cannot be guessed easily and to safeguard those passwords from disclosure. Please contact us if you have any information regarding unauthorized use of the Sling Products.

Changes to this Privacy Statement:   

We may make changes to this Privacy Statement from time to time for any reason. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Statement in effect at the time such information is used (though you always have the option to delete your account as described above). If we make changes in the way we use Personally Identifiable Information, we will notify you via e-mail or by posting an announcement on our website. The latest version will be available at http://www.slingbox.com/get/privacy-policy. You will be bound by any changes to the Privacy Statement when you use Sling Products after receiving notice of such changes.

Effective Date:  The Effective Date of this Privacy Statement is December 17, 2007
